<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Breastfeeding on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</title>
    <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/tags/breastfeeding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Breastfeeding on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:40:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wendyhackermom.com/tags/breastfeeding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned from my first two months as a working mom</title>
      <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-12-15-two-month-working-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:40:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-12-15-two-month-working-mom/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been back at work from maternity leave for about 2 months now. It&amp;rsquo;s been a journey coming back to work, to say the least.
First of all, I&amp;rsquo;m SO HAPPY to be back at work! I took exactly 3 months of leave, and will save the rest of the baby-bonding leave for a family trip to Taiwan for 4 weeks. For me, the first month of leave was necessary for the body to recover, and the second month was more of a getting-to-know-the-baby time, and the third month was the real baby-bonding, mainly on sleep training the baby, learning to get out of the house and travel a bit, and that was when I started to crave for human (adult) interaction and when I started to write this blog :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Breastfeeding vs Formula is just like Tabs vs Spaces</title>
      <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-11-06-tabs-spaces-breastfeeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:46:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-11-06-tabs-spaces-breastfeeding/</guid>
      <description>For the first month of my baby&amp;rsquo;s life, I struggled through the whole breastfeeding thing. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go into too much details, so some bullet points of events/struggles:
 The baby was born early (but full term), so he was very sleepy, preferred sleeping over eating.
 He wasn&amp;rsquo;t latching on correctly (although, he was always too sleepy to actually tell if he had a good latch or not).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>