<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</title>
    <link>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 22:14:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Lose Pregnancy Weight by Not Gaining Weight</title>
      <link>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/2018-10-02-how-to-lose-weight-by-not-gaining-weight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 22:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/2018-10-02-how-to-lose-weight-by-not-gaining-weight/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve never been on a diet except when I was pregnant. That seems ironic, since people usually look at pregnancy as the once chance in a woman&amp;rsquo;s life to indulge and to &amp;ldquo;eat whatever you want&amp;rdquo;. This seems particularly prominent in American culture - &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re eating for two!&amp;rdquo; etc.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always been very active - I was a basketball player in both high school and college. Played volleyball and also picked up rock climbing in grad school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will I be so bored at my maternity/paternity leave?</title>
      <link>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/2018-09-29-what-can-be-done-parental-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 01:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/2018-09-29-what-can-be-done-parental-leave/</guid>
      <description>The anxiety Months before I even started my maternity leave, I felt very anxious about that &amp;ldquo;break time&amp;rdquo;: what would it be like? Would it be just me and the baby sitting at home, me slaving away, desperately waiting for anyone to come rescue us? I started asking people questions about what they do at this time.
 Friend A: Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you&amp;rsquo;ll be SO BUSY with the baby, you won&amp;rsquo;t even worry about what to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I started this blog</title>
      <link>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/why-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 13:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techparent-98fe5.firebaseapp.com/post/why-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I never imagined myself as someone who shares parenting advice. Growing up, I&amp;rsquo;m simply not a &amp;ldquo;mom type&amp;rdquo;. In fact, for most of the time in my life, I did not want children - I am simply too career focused, persuing an intellectual lifestyle; so chasing after a toddler and being bothered with milk supply didn&amp;rsquo;t seem like my thing.
So why am I blogging now? Well, after I married a great guy, we started to dream about having a family.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>