<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Motherhood on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</title>
    <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/tags/motherhood/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Motherhood on Wendy&#39;s Hacker Mom Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:40:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wendyhackermom.com/tags/motherhood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons learned from my first two months as a working mom</title>
      <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-12-15-two-month-working-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 16:40:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-12-15-two-month-working-mom/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been back at work from maternity leave for about 2 months now. It&amp;rsquo;s been a journey coming back to work, to say the least.
First of all, I&amp;rsquo;m SO HAPPY to be back at work! I took exactly 3 months of leave, and will save the rest of the baby-bonding leave for a family trip to Taiwan for 4 weeks. For me, the first month of leave was necessary for the body to recover, and the second month was more of a getting-to-know-the-baby time, and the third month was the real baby-bonding, mainly on sleep training the baby, learning to get out of the house and travel a bit, and that was when I started to crave for human (adult) interaction and when I started to write this blog :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I came to embrace being a mom</title>
      <link>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-10-19-how-i-embrace-being-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 23:19:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wendyhackermom.com/post/2018-10-19-how-i-embrace-being-mom/</guid>
      <description>This is a strange topic to write. I feel like by writing this, I&amp;rsquo;m going to seem like the reluctant mom, where my pregnancy was unplanned. But it&amp;rsquo;s the opposite - the pregnancy was very much looked forward to. So, one would find it hard to discover that&amp;hellip;
I never wanted to be a mom.
I wanted to maybe have children, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the fact that having children would, inevitably, make me a mother.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>